<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
	<title>Reuters News</title>
	<link></link>
	<description>Reuters.com is your source for breaking news, business, financial and investing news, including personal finance and stocks.  Reuters is the leading global provider of news, financial information and technology solutions to the world's media, financial institutions, businesses and individuals.</description>
	<language>en-us</language>
	<copyright>All rights reserved. Users may download and print extracts of content from this website for their own personal and non-commercial use only. Republication or redistribution of Reuters content, including by framing or similar means, is expressly prohibited without the prior written consent of Reuters. Reuters and the Reuters sphere logo are registered trademarks or trademarks of the Reuters group of companies around the world. © Reuters 2019</copyright>
	<pubdate></pubdate>
<item>
	<title>Movie Review: Ek Ladki Ko Dekha Toh Aisa Laga</title>
	<description>Shelly Chopra Dhar’s "Ek Ladki Ko Dekha Toh Aisa Laga" (What I Felt when I Saw that Girl) is much like a package ordered from Amazon. The box is huge, but most of the volume is because of the wrapping material, which can sometimes leave you a bit disappointed with the size of the actual product.</description>
	<link>http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INbollywood/~3/KBEOcu56vDA/movie-review-ek-ladki-ko-dekha-toh-aisa-laga-idINKCN1PQ4NZ</link>
	<author></author>
	<guid>https://in.reuters.com/article/movie-review-ek-ladki-ko-dekha-toh-aisa/movie-review-ek-ladki-ko-dekha-toh-aisa-laga-idINKCN1PQ4NZ?feedType=RSS</guid>

</item>
<item>
	<title>Movie Review: Thackeray</title>
	<description>Before the opening credits of Abhijit Panse’s “Thackeray”, a somber voice reads out that the film does not intend to hurt anyone’s feelings, defame anyone, or endorse any sort of violence. This last disclaimer is crucial, because throughout the film, especially the scene leading up to the climax, the subject of the biopic, Bal Thackeray, goes against this very principle.</description>
	<link>http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INbollywood/~3/mApZtPBcFNY/movie-review-thackeray-idINKCN1PJ15G</link>
	<author></author>
	<guid>https://in.reuters.com/article/movie-review-thackeray/movie-review-thackeray-idINKCN1PJ15G?feedType=RSS</guid>

</item>
<item>
	<title>Movie Review - Manikarnika: The Queen of Jhansi</title>
	<description>It is apparent that Kangana Ranaut wears the pants in this period drama – both on and off the screen. The actress is credited as the film’s co-director and she seems to have the reins of control firmly in her hands, whether she is riding a horse or wielding the director’s baton.</description>
	<link>http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INbollywood/~3/2vd3LuTp67A/movie-review-manikarnika-the-queen-of-jhansi-idINKCN1PJ0I5</link>
	<author></author>
	<guid>https://in.reuters.com/article/movie-review-bollywood-manikarnika/movie-review-manikarnika-the-queen-of-jhansi-idINKCN1PJ0I5?feedType=RSS</guid>

</item>
<item>
	<title>Q</title>
	<description>REUTERS - From playing a gangster in Netflix’s “Sacred Games” to portraying the Pakistani poet Saadat Hasan Manto on the big screen, actor Nawazuddin Siddiqui has received acclaim for most of his roles in an almost 20-year career. His latest film sees him playing one of his more challenging and controversial roles – that of the late Bal Thackeray, one of India’s most polarising politicians.</description>
	<link>http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INbollywood/~3/geAiY-UKO9Q/qa-thackeray-actor-nawazuddin-siddiqui-on-why-he-doesnt-have-an-ideology-idINKCN1PH0HZ</link>
	<author></author>
	<guid>https://in.reuters.com/article/interview-nawazuddin-siddiqui-thackeray/qa-thackeray-actor-nawazuddin-siddiqui-on-why-he-doesnt-have-an-ideology-idINKCN1PH0HZ?feedType=RSS</guid>

</item>
<item>
	<title>Movie Review: Why Cheat India</title>
	<description>Soumik Sen’s drama starring Emraan Hashmi is a rough-at-the-edges but surprisingly perceptive look at the dysfunctional education system in India and the losing battle that millions of students fight to get on the right side of it. Through his unscrupulous, but resourceful protagonist, Sen gives us an insight into the middle class’s obsession with competitive exams as a means for a better life.</description>
	<link>http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INbollywood/~3/q0WtwyTpLcw/movie-review-why-cheat-india-idINKCN1PC0OJ</link>
	<author></author>
	<guid>https://in.reuters.com/article/bollywood-moviereview-whycheatindia/movie-review-why-cheat-india-idINKCN1PC0OJ?feedType=RSS</guid>

</item>
<item>
	<title>Movie Review: The Accidental Prime Minister</title>
	<description>At one point in Vijay Gutte’s “The Accidental Prime Minister”, the usually reticent and socially awkward Manmohan Singh tells his outgoing media adviser Sanjaya Baru “ek jhappi toh paa le” (give me a hug) and stands up to give him a rather effusive embrace. It’s difficult to imagine Singh saying those words, but then so much about this film seems staged that you wouldn’t know the real from the reel.</description>
	<link>http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INbollywood/~3/z12MKHU7kmo/movie-review-the-accidental-prime-minister-idINKCN1P5105</link>
	<author></author>
	<guid>https://in.reuters.com/article/movie-review-accidental-prime-minister/movie-review-the-accidental-prime-minister-idINKCN1P5105?feedType=RSS</guid>

</item>
<item>
	<title>Movie Review - Uri: The Surgical Strike</title>
	<description>(REUTERS) - Opposition politicians in India might have been skeptical of the army's much-touted “surgical strike” across the border in 2016, but director Aditya Dhar has no such doubts. Thankfully, he has the directing skills to match his belief.</description>
	<link>http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INbollywood/~3/PgHleEABHic/movie-review-uri-the-surgical-strike-idINKCN1P50MT</link>
	<author></author>
	<guid>https://in.reuters.com/article/movie-review-uri/movie-review-uri-the-surgical-strike-idINKCN1P50MT?feedType=RSS</guid>

</item>
<item>
	<title>Q</title>
	<description>REUTERS - In 2016, Aditya Dhar was busy prepping for his directorial debut which was to star Pakistani actor Fawad Khan when militants stormed an Indian army base in Kashmir. With New Delhi blaming its neighbour for the attack which killed 17 soldiers, many Bollywood producers declared that they will no longer work with Pakistani actors, which led to the shelving of Dhar’s project.</description>
	<link>http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INbollywood/~3/UmWAppbxwKU/qa-aditya-dhar-on-uri-the-surgical-strike-idINKCN1P50J3</link>
	<author></author>
	<guid>https://in.reuters.com/article/interview-aditya-dhar-uri/qa-aditya-dhar-on-uri-the-surgical-strike-idINKCN1P50J3?feedType=RSS</guid>

</item>
<item>
	<title>Bollywood film on former PM Manmohan Singh stirs controversy before election</title>
	<description>A film that casts opposition leader Rahul Gandhi and his family in an unflattering light ahead of a national election later this year has kicked up a controversy ahead of its release on Friday.</description>
	<link>http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INbollywood/~3/9b8ndU5onNk/bollywood-film-on-form</link>
	<author></author>
	<guid>https://in.reuters.com/article/election-bollywood-manmohansingh/bollywood-film-on-former-pm-manmohan-singh-stirs-controversy-before-election-idINKCN1P31AW?feedType=RSS</guid>

</item>
<item>
	<title>Movie Review: Zero</title>
	<description>In a pivotal scene in Aanand L. Rai’s “Zero”, protagonist Bauua Singh is trying to pull off his most famous magic trick - making a star fall from the sky - in front of an eager crowd. It’s a trick he knows well and has performed hundreds of times, but this time, it doesn’t work.</description>
	<link>http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INbollywood/~3/vi0pb23idfA/movie-review-zero-idINKCN1OK0MK</link>
	<author></author>
	<guid>https://in.reuters.com/article/movie-review-zero/movie-review-zero-idINKCN1OK0MK?feedType=RSS</guid>

</item>
<item>
	<title>Hillary Clinton joins Bollywood stars as super-rich Indians wed</title>
	<description>The daughter of India's richest man got married on Wednesday in a traditional ceremony in Mumbai attended by Bollywood stars and former U.S. presidential candidate Hillary Clinton.</description>
	<link>http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INbollywood/~3/zqC2yl2TwSo/hillary-clinton-joins-bollywood-stars-as-super-rich-indians-wed-idINKBN1OB2FF</link>
	<author></author>
	<guid>https://in.reuters.com/article/india-ambani-marriage/hillary-clinton-joins-bollywood-stars-as-super-rich-indians-wed-idINKBN1OB2FF?feedType=RSS</guid>

</item>
<item>
	<title>Movie-mad India could overtake U.S. as top user-base - IMDb</title>
	<description>Movie-mad Indians and the cheap data packs on their smartphones could make India the biggest user-base market for IMDb over the next five years, the Amazon-owned movie rating website said on Wednesday.</description>
	<link>http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INbollywood/~3/fxZzvLe_43k/movie-mad-india-could-overtake-u-s-as-top-user-base-imdb-idINKBN1OB1V1</link>
	<author></author>
	<guid>https://in.reuters.com/article/movies-india/movie-mad-india-could-overtake-u-s-as-top-user-base-imdb-idINKBN1OB1V1?feedType=RSS</guid>

</item>
<item>
	<title>Movie Review: Kedarnath</title>
	<description>In Abhishek Kapoor’s “Kedarnath”, the forces of nature collide with the force of young love, and you get a tale that seeks to marry themes of faith, religion, intolerance and the destruction of the environment.</description>
	<link>http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INbollywood/~3/huhMzyZul14/movie-review-kedarnath-idINKBN1O60T3</link>
	<author></author>
	<guid>https://in.reuters.com/article/movie-review-kedarnath/movie-review-kedarnath-idINKBN1O60T3?feedType=RSS</guid>

</item>
<item>
	<title>It’s the script, stupid: Junglee Pictures looks beyond stars to churn out hits</title>
	<description>Reuters - As Bollywood makes its year-end report card, one film that will emerge as the standout hit of 2018 is “Badhaai Ho” (Congratulations). The comedy-drama has made 1. 35 billion rupee</description>
	<link>http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INbollywood/~3/LZv6Um8dHE8/its-the-script-stupid-junglee-pictures-looks-beyond-stars-to-churn-out-hits-idINKBN1O60MM</link>
	<author></author>
	<guid>https://in.reuters.com/article/bollywood-junglee-pictures/its-the-script-stupid-junglee-pictures-looks-beyond-stars-to-churn-out-hits-idINKBN1O60MM?feedType=RSS</guid>

</item>
<item>
	<title>Priyanka Chopra, Nick Jonas celebrate wedding at New Delhi reception</title>
	<description>Priyanka Chopra, star of Indian film and U.S. television, and Jonas Brothers singer Nick Jonas celebrated their wedding at a glitzy reception in New Delhi on Tuesday, joined by celebrities ranging from India's prime minister to Hollywood stars.</description>
	<link>http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INbollywood/~3/t3T1OYDLXtg/priyanka-chopra-nick-jonas-celebrate-wedding-at-new-delhi-reception-idINKBN1O40G1</link>
	<author></author>
	<guid>https://in.reuters.com/article/people-nickjonas-chopra/priyanka-chopra-nick-jonas-celebrate-wedding-at-new-delhi-reception-idINKBN1O40G1?feedType=RSS</guid>

</item>
<item>
	<title>Priyanka Chopra, Nick Jonas to marry in traditional Hindu ceremony</title>
	<description>"Quantico" actor Priyanka Chopra and U.S. singer Nick Jonas will be married in a traditional Hindu ceremony today, the culmination of a three-day long wedding celebration that featured cricket matches and Bollywood songs, all taking place in a heritage Indian palace atop a hill.</description>
	<link>http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INbollywood/~3/Xqg72YjCneY/priyanka-chopra-nick-jonas-to-marry-in-traditional-hindu-ceremony-idINKBN1O10E2</link>
	<author></author>
	<guid>https://in.reuters.com/article/people-nickjonas-chopra/priyanka-chopra-nick-jonas-to-marry-in-traditional-hindu-ceremony-idINKBN1O10E2?feedType=RSS</guid>

</item>
<item>
	<title>Priyanka Chopra, Nick Jonas marry in Jodhpur palace - People magazine</title>
	<description>"Quantico" actor and Bollywood star Priyanka Chopra married U.S singer Nick Jonas on Saturday in a Christian ceremony attended by close family and friends at one of India's most opulent royal palaces, People magazine reported.</description>
	<link>http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INbollywood/~3/TEvUIl_gumM/priyanka-chopra-nick-jonas-marry-in-jodhpur-palace-people-magazine-idINKCN1O03FA</link>
	<author></author>
	<guid>https://in.reuters.com/article/people-nickjonas-chopra/priyanka-chopra-nick-jonas-marry-in-jodhpur-palace-people-magazine-idINKCN1O03FA?feedType=RSS</guid>

</item>
<item>
	<title>Movie Review: 2.0</title>
	<description>Director Shankar should be applauded for the idea behind "2.0". The idea of the most ubiquitous thing in our lives - the cellphone - turning on humanity and causing destruction makes for great entertainment and is instantly relatable to an audience that presumably cannot resist glancing at their mobile devices during the film's screening.</description>
	<link>http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INbollywood/~3/EQVl5MkInQo/movie-review-2-0-idINKCN1NY209</link>
	<author></author>
	<guid>https://in.reuters.com/article/2pointo-robot-rajinikanth-pakshi/movie-review-2-0-idINKCN1NY209?feedType=RSS</guid>

</item>
<item>
	<title>Q</title>
	<description>From sharing screen space with Judi Dench in “Victoria </description>
	<link>http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INbollywood/~3/-rBVHBbgoPs/qa-indian-filmmakers-cant-get-away-with-mediocrity-anymore-ali-fazal-idINKCN1NY0G6</link>
	<author></author>
	<guid>https://in.reuters.com/article/interview-ali-fazal-mirzapur/qa-indian-filmmakers-cant-get-away-with-mediocrity-anymore-ali-fazal-idINKCN1NY0G6?feedType=RSS</guid>

</item>
<item>
	<title>Movie Review: Pihu</title>
	<description>For anyone who’s grown up watching the “Home Alone” series, a movie about a child being left alone at home would bring back memories of funny moments, emotional scenes and a happy ending.</description>
	<link>http://feeds.reuters.com/~r/reuters/INbollywood/~3/CHutig_v62I/movie-review-pihu-idINKCN1NL0VZ</link>
	<author></author>
	<guid>https://in.reuters.com/article/bollywood-moviereview-pihu/movie-review-pihu-idINKCN1NL0VZ?feedType=RSS</guid>

</item>

</channel>
</rss>
